st-hubert.com 2015-12-10

# Privacy policy

### **STATEMENT OF POLICY**

Groupe St-Hubert inc. ("St-Hubert") considers the care and protection of your personal and private information to be of utmost importance and has integrated tight measures to protect your private information. With the goal of ensuring that your rights in this area are fully respected, St-Hubert has designed a policy that clearly outlines this privacy protection.

In connection with the operation of the [www.st-hubert.com](http://www.st-hubert.com/) website, St-Hubert must collect, use, and communicate private information to properly process orders placed via the website. This privacy policy establishes the principles on which the information you supply to us is protected.

By private information St-Hubert means all information that pertains to a physical person and confirms his/her identity.

###  **Collection of private information**

St-Hubert only collects information necessary to process orders placed by users on the [www.st-hubert.com](http://www.st-hubert.com/) website. As such, St-Hubert requires that you transmit your first and last names, your email address, your password, your full address, your telephone number, address of delivery. St-Hubert may also collect other, non-mandatory information.

###  **Use of private information**

St-Hubert intends to use the private information gathered only to open an account under your name, process your order, deploy delivery of your order and, if you permit, to periodically send you personalized information regarding our website and products. Your personal information is only available to employees when such knowledge is necessary to fulfilling the job duties required to complete the above order process.

St-Hubert neither commercializes nor communicates the list of people using the [www.st-hubert.com](http://www.st-hubert.com/) website.

###  **Transmitting private information**

Within the framework of processing an order, St-Hubert must communicate certain private information to different branches so that they can complete and deliver your order. The information shared is: your name, your delivery address, and your telephone number.

By using the [www.st-hubert.com](http://www.st-hubert.com/) website, you allow St-Hubert to communicate this information to employees at the different rotisseries. St-Hubert also reserves the right to transmit private information in a situation where obliged by law or to protect its interests or that of its users or suppliers.

###  **Security measures**

St-Hubert has implanted security measures designed to ensure full protection against loss or unauthorized use of the information you provide to St-Hubert.

St-Hubert's servers utilise Secure Socket Layers (SSL), the most up-to-date and secure transmission technology available. All private data is encrypted by the SSL the moment it is entered, making it impossible to read during transfer to the Internet. This security service is certified by VeriSign.

While selecting your items and placing your order, you are able to verify whether the webpage is secure by checking to see if the URL web address starts with https:// and that there is the icon of a lock in the bottom right of your navigation screen.

St-Hubert's servers are protected by firewall technology. St-Hubert is committed to cutting-edge technology that provides totally secure online transactions.

###  **Conserving private information**

St-Hubert conserves private information in conformity with the laws concerning protection of personal information.

If you no longer want to receive information about St-Hubert and its products, you can opt-out by checking the corresponding box on your "Profile" page.

###  **Viewing and modifying personal information**

At any time you may consult and edit the information in your "profile". Simply go to the home page of www.st-hubert.com and log in with your email address and password. You will then see a hyperlink ("My Profile") in the top right corner of the page. Click there to view and update your personal information.

###  **Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file left on your hard drive by some web pages. Cookies are unobtrusive and cannot read or extract any information from your computer. St-Hubert utilizes cookies to preserve your active navigation session for a pre-established time period. This technology does not systematically gather personal data on you for St-Hubert. You can always choose to disallow cookies by modifying the configuration of your computer.

###  **Contact us**

For all questions, comments, and/or complaints, we invite you to contact us. 

  * By phone: (514) 385-3916 (Montréal) 
  * By filling out the [contact form](http://www.st-hubert.com/entreprise/nous-joindre/formulaire-contact.en.html) on our Website
  * By mail: CSC 2500, Daniel-Johnson Blvd., Suite 700, Laval (Québec) H7T 2P6.
